https://www.dag.com/privacy-policy

Support
About
Blog
Privacy Policy
Overview:
Data Advantage Group, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and personal space. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.dag.com.
We use your IP address and anonymous information about your Internet browser and operating system to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer/enhance our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information - we will not personally identify you to this particular address. This site contains links to other sites. Data Advantage Group, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Our online surveys and forms ask visitors for contact information (including: name, email address, title, company, address, phone number). We use contact data from these forms to send users information about our company, products and services. This information is collected on a voluntary basis and you my decline in submitting it at any time. We store this information on your computer in a "cookie". Therefore, in order for certain portions of our site to operate correctly, you must have your browser set to accept cookies. From time to time we may share this information with our partners and resellers.
To modify this information at anytime, send an email with the changes to us or re-submit the information using the online forms.
Security:
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Such security measures are firewalls and passwords. While it is never possible to protect a site 100%, we will do our best to make sure your browsing experience is safe and will correct any problems as soon as possible.
Modifications:
This privacy may be updated from time to time to reflect new or changed regulations. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified when you registered at our site or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Contacting the Web Site Administrator:
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us.
What We Do
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] MetaCenter
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] Resources
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] Support
About Us
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] Company
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] Contact Us
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] Blog
[fa icon="angle-double-right"] Privacy Policy
Data Advantage Group, Inc.
Data Advantage Group is a leading provider of enterprise metadata management and data governance solutions. Our MetaCenter platform enables organizations to govern their information assets while lowering costs, improving agility and reducing operational risks.
Contact Us
[fa icon="phone"]  +1 (415) 947-0400
[fa icon="envelope"]  info@dag.com
[fa icon="home"]  145 Natoma St
San Francisco CA
Copyright 2020 | Designed with
[fa icon="heart"]
in San Francisco
[fa icon="chevron-up"]
